Hi! Welcome to my channel! No, just kidding. No name for my channel yet, but hi again.
Welcome to this video. I received a bunch of clothing items from Fates and I thought I'm
going to do my first clothing haul ever. Yeah, I hope I pronounce haul in the right way because
is really a weird word. So I'm going to show you a few pieces I received by face
and I hope you'll have fun. So one of the first pieces is this top which is a bit
shiny and a bit lazy and surprise I'm going to wear it now. So this is a really
cool basic top just I don't know like you can wear it beneath a corset or just wear it for clubbing.
So it's really comfy with the combination of PVC and mesh a bit of see-through and there is a second
version of this top which is completely made of mesh so with the PVC on the straps. I think I'll
I'll just wear a bra underneath it because it's a bit see-through but that's the fun, right?
So two basic skirts, one with a bit of lace and what's this called? Lacing? Yeah, lace and lacing
on the skirt. The backside is PVC as well. It's a tiny basic skirt so to say. As well
as this one with PVC. Put these playful O-rings on the sides of the skirt. Bunch of corsets,
I never thought I'm into brocade but I think the combination of black and
purple is really awesome this is an over bust corset and it's kind of heavy so I
think there's a little boning inside so this one is yeah I don't know yet how
I'm going to combine it because it's leopard fur imitation whatever
stylish and I normally don't wear that kind of clothing but I sure come up
with something funny or I don't know yet to be honest
But therefore this one is really beauty.
A PVC and ribbons corset.
Ribbons?
Yeah.
Anyway it's PVC, it's shiny, it's totally what I like to wear.
I'm going to combine it with a nice skirt I guess.
And some gothy makeup.
I think this is going to be fun.
And another corset I received is this one.
It's pink and white.
So I think it's even more unusual for me than the Leopard 1.
Here, thanks Faggy's that you're trusting me to pull this off and to look good in this
one.
going to be... I'm going to try my best.
It's pink.
I'm super excited about this skirt because it's green and it's kind of... what is it?
It's much harder than PVC, it's like plastic or whatever. Yeah it's stiffer than PVC for sure.
but it looks just really awesome and really shiny and green as well as this
one which is the same material in red and it's by Golden Steampunk which is a
sub brand of face but I think they're really cool I think I'm going to combine
them with something black because they're a lot of color to deal with but
I like them. Still in its plastic wrap. More PVC! Looks pretty small. So it's a top with
long arms. Since there are a lot of skirts I'm really happy to combine this one
with all the PVC skirts I own thanks to face. I'm sure this is going to be a nice
addition to my wardrobe and it's really shiny. It looks really tight though. Let's
see if I'm going to fit in. So it fits. The arms are long, that's nice. It's a bit
short but I'm sure if I'm going to wear it beneath a corset or with a skirt it'll
all just be fine but overall I think it's really nice yeah it's short for me
because I'm tall. Maybe. So another top that came with the whole package is cute lace
straps top with the face thingy with a cameo. Cameo and drone I don't know what's it
So it looks really cute. I'm sure it'll fit on a bunch of skirts or leggings.
A BBC catsuit! Super cool. I'm not going to put this on now, but maybe I'll do a
dressing video with the corset. Let's see about that. But now I can do a full face
corset catsuit outfit and the... No, there's no zipper in the crotch, so...
I hope this is going to fit because I'm tall and the wood looks just fine.
Okay, it's a shrug.
Shrugs are super cool to put on top of corsets to cover your shoulders to just complete any
outfit basically.
And I'm super happy to finally own something I can just put on top.
And it has this cute lacing on the back side so it's adjustable and with all the zipper
around it looks really cool.
So if you liked this video then click on the like button or whatever, comment on it, share
it.
I would really appreciate it if you want me to do other videos then I'm happy about your feedback.
That's what I was looking for.
Because I'm not sure yet if I will continue doing videos.
It was fun, it was interesting to do and maybe there will be another video soon.